Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; 6; 22929
  - Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; 6.1; 22929
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/22/08 at 2:30 p.m. for Interim President George Philip addressing the Spring Faculty in the Campus Center Ballroom., 2008 May 5; 9.4 MB 27
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/24/08 at 10:00 a.m. with Alex Angel, the AED Coordinator for the SUNY Lifesaver program., 2008 May 5; 31.5 MB 26
    - Major Gifts: Photo session: 5/5/08 @ 5:00 for the Great Dane Awards reception, 2008 May 5; 81.3 MB 167
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 5/5/08 @ l:30 for Climate Commitment signing at the courtyard in front of the Social Sciences building., 2008 May 5; 57.6 MB 38
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 5/5/08 @ l:30 for Climate Commitment signing at the courtyard in front of the Social Sciences building., 2008 May 5; 57.6 MB 38
    - Media and Marketing: 4/15/08 @ 8 pm CC 375 National Society of Collegiate Scholars; Integity Day, 2008 May 5; 96.1 MB 56
    - Research: Photo session: 4/24/08 from 12:00 to 4:00 for the 9th Annual Research Colloquium at the Life Sciences Research Building., 2008 May 6; 43.4 MB 84
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 5/6/08 @ 3:30 p.m. with Dan Willard for the Excellence Awards., 2008 May 6; 13.4 MB 29
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 5/6/08 @ 3:30 p.m. with Dan Willard for the Excellence Awards., 2008 May 6; 13.4 MB 29
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 5/7/08 @ 3:30 p.m. Candace Merbler for the Excellence Awards., 2008 May 7; 37.5 MB 27
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 5/7/08 @ 3:30 p.m. Candace Merbler for the Excellence Awards., 2008 May 7; 37.5 MB 27
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 5/15/08 @ 9:30 a.m. E. Stewart Jones at the Cancer Center on the East Campus., 2008 May 15; 35.5 MB 73
    - Rockefeller College: Photo Session: 5/16/08 from 2:00-5:00PM Graduate Recognition Ceremony@ Rockefeller College, Page Hall, 2008 May 16; 717.5 MB 124
    - Special Projects: Photo session: 5/17/08 from 11:30 am to 12:30 pm in the BA Building, 2008 May 17; 329.4 MB 56
    - University Libraries: Photo session: 5/20/08 from 2 - 4 pm in the Standish Room for the Bread 'n Roses event., 2008 May 20; 92.4 MB 134
    - President's Office: Photo session: 5/21/08 @ 12:00 p.m. in UNH 300 for the Student Exchange Agreement., 2008 May 26; 23.1 MB 58
    - UPD_Bike Patrol Class, 2008 June 5; 47.3 MB 104
    - Train Station Installation, 2008 July 8; 114.1 MB 40
    - Bruno_Albany Med Announcement, 2008 July 14; 34.3 MB 104
    - IBM Press Conference, 2008 July 15; 94.0 MB 176
    - NEPHLI_2008, 2008 July 16; 52.4 MB 113
    - Asian Delegation, 2008 July 19; 49.2 MB 28
    - New Ambulance, 2008 August 14; 19.7 MB 38
    - Red Cross Blood Donor Award, 2008 August 21; 21.5 MB 13
    - Entry Plaza Dedication, 2008 August 27; 42.2 MB 104
    - CARSS_press conference, 2008 September 4; 32.8 MB 57
    - Global Health Press Conference, 2008 September 10; 14.6 MB 15
    - Study Abroad Fair, 2008 September 10; 36.8 MB 69
    - New Ambulance_wet down, 2008 September 17; 44.3 MB 102
    - Constitution Day_08, 2008 September 18; 13.8 MB 27
    - Kenneth Hall Lecture_Jamaican Governor General, 2008 September 18; 91.3 MB 159
    - Governor General of Jamaica_Kenneth Hall, 2008 September 18; 22.7 MB 28
    - Constitution Day_08, 2008 September 18; 13.8 MB 27
    - Cancer Center Open House, 2008 October 3; 51.5 MB 82
    - Truchan, Dan, 2008 October 4; 22.7 MB 48
    - Hong Kong Baptist University Delegation, 2008 October 10; 14.6 MB 43
    - Tula University Delegation, 2008 October 22; 68.0 MB 98
    - light bulbs to students, 2008 October 23; 31.1 MB 63
    - Leonard Marcus, 2008 October 24; 20.5 MB 48
    - Leonard Marcus, 2008 October 24; 20.5 MB 48
    - Alumni Awareness Luncheon_08, 2008 October 25; 97.7 MB 225
    - Alumni Awareness Luncheon_08, 2008 October 25; 97.7 MB 225
    - UAlbany Day_08, 2008 October 26; 67.9 MB 33
    - Amanda Fields and Committee, 2008 November 6; 18.0 MB 44
    - NEA, 2008 November 6; 31.5 MB 65
    - Autism Conference, 2008 November 7; 75.6 MB 123
    - Council for Economic Outreach, 2008 November 12; 55.5 MB 88
    - ODK_Bill Johnston, 2008 November 18; 53.6 MB 107
    - Citizen Laureate_08, 2008 November 20; 149.9 MB 209
    - Chancellor's Awards, 2008 November 22; 22.0 MB 50
    - Chancellor's Awards, 2008 November 22; 22.0 MB 50
    - Fillipone Check Presentaion, 2008 November 26; 25.0 MB 38
    - University Holiday Event, 2008 December 10; 59.4 MB 68
    - Key Bank Check Presentation, 2008 December 18; 15.9 MB 28
    - Ushers Machine and Tool, 2008 December 24; 52.3 MB 44
    - Donald Faulkner_Writers Institute, 2009 January 14; 24.9 MB 49
    - Women in Gov't_Fellowship, 2009 January 16; 94.3 MB 61
    - NYBuzz Press Conference, 2009 February 4; 64.7 MB 110
    - Dr. Pogue_MLK Luncheon, 2009 February 6; 36.6 MB 73
    - Denis Hayes lecture, 2009 February 10; 17.2 MB 49
    - Advocacy Day_09, 2009 February 11; 99.8 MB 241
    - Advocacy Day_09, 2009 February 11; 99.8 MB 241
    - Paint Your Campus Purple, 2009 February 24; 101.5 MB 67
    - Schumer Press Conf, 2009 February 24; 317.7 MB 64
    - Counseling Center, 2009 February 25; 23.7 MB 49
    - Disability Resource Center Fundraiser, 2009 February 26; 24.6 MB 43
    - Community Engagement Forum, 2009 March 2; 84.1 MB 134
    - Pitney_Bowes, 2009 March 10; 43.5 MB 94
    - Tech Valley High School, 2009 March 19; 119.1 MB 176
    - new faculty agreement signing, 2009 March 21; 26.4 MB 43
    - Dominion Foundation Luncheon, 2009 March 25; 102.6 MB 154
    - ribbon cutting event, 2009 March 31; 177.1 MB 92
    - Employee Recognition Dessert Reception, 2009 April 1; 58.6 MB 82
    - Employee Recognition Luncheon, 2009 April 1; 36.3 MB 42
    - Chancellors Award Recipients, 2009 April 3; 69.3 MB 16
    - Healthy Hearts on the Hill, 2009 April 24; 51.0 MB 84
    - Fountain Day 2009, 2009 April 27; 1.4 GB 383
    - Burton Lecture 2009, 2009 April 29; 106.7 MB 168
    - Latin Barometer, 2009 May 5; 40.3 MB 95
    - Great Dane Awards_09, 2009 May 5; 72.6 MB 123
    - William Powers Scholarship Check, 2009 May 6; 7.9 MB 18
    - Excellence Awards 2009, 2009 May 7; 99.7 MB 28
    - Picnic, 2009 May 17; 12.2 MB 20
    - Bread and Roses 2009, 2009 May 21; 25.6 MB 68
    - Chancellor Nancy Zimpher Visit, 2009 June 4; 894.4 MB 453
    - Chancellor Nancy Zimpher Visit, 2009 June 5; 894.4 MB 453
    - Chancellor Nancy Zimpher Visit, 2009 June 5; 894.4 MB 453
    - press conference announcing Undergrad degree program, 2009 June 13; 96.7 MB 181
    - UAlbany Foundation Board Meeting and Donor Reception, 2009 June 18; 151.5 MB 226
    - Visiting Chinese Faculty, 2009 July 15; 47.3 MB 19
    - NEPHLI, 2009 July 15; 61.5 MB 117
    - Fulbright Gateway Orientation, 2009 August 3; 67.3 MB 29
    - FulbrightGateway_state capital, 2009 August 6; 56.4 MB 53
    - Ice Cream Social, 2009 September 2; 112.5 MB 64
    - Energy Campaign_CFL kickoff, 2009 September 4; 180.8 MB 42
    - Shabbos House, 2009 September 5; 75.9 MB 41
    - Accounting Orientation for Juniors, 2009 September 9; 117.2 MB 144
    - Aids Walk, 2009 September 11; 112.2 MB 73
    - 694_2382.jpg, 2009 September 15; 6.5 MB 10
    - Sustainability Fair_Press Conference, 2009 September 23; 162.8 MB 260
    - Sustainability Fair_Press Conference, 2009 September 23; 162.8 MB 260
    - Career_Fair_09, 2009 September 24; 76.3 MB 41
    - Tech Valley HS Opening, 2009 October 1; 141.8 MB 79
    - George McGovern Visit, 2009 October 1; 28.5 MB 33
    - George McGovern Visit, 2009 October 1; 28.5 MB 33
    - K-9 Unit, 2009 October 7; 70.7 MB 119
    - Glen Browder_Steve Kuykendall, 2009 October 8; 57.0 MB 118
    - UAlbany_Community_Day09, 2009 October 10; 796.1 MB 401
    - Colin Powell, 2009 October 11; 356.2 MB 325
    - UAlbany_Community_Day09, 2009 October 11; 796.1 MB 401
    - Colin Powell, 2009 October 11; 356.2 MB 325
    - OASAS, 2009 October 21; 211.3 MB 115
    - Bailey Memorial Anniversary, 2009 October 22; 118.7 MB 56
    - Citizen Laureate09, 2009 October 23; 120.2 MB 199
    - PAD507, 2009 October 24; 227.4 MB 159
    - Business Leaders Breakfast, 2009 October 28; 106.0 MB 163
    - press conference_Cancer Center, 2009 October 29; 24.8 MB 53
    - SA Rally, 2009 November 7; 188.5 MB 109
    - Education Reform Discussion, 2009 November 10; 150.0 MB 266
    - Education Reform Discussion, 2009 November 11; 150.0 MB 266
    - Nanjing Univ Delegation, 2009 November 17; 27.6 MB 59
    - Writers Institute 25th Aniversary Celebration, 2009 November 17; 230.2 MB 283
    - Writers Institute 25th Aniversary Celebration, 2009 November 17; 230.2 MB 283
    - Holiday Card set-up, 2009 November 18; 448.1 MB 213
    - Holiday Card set-up, 2009 November 18; 132.3 MB 54
    - check presentation_Key Bank, 2009 November 19; 11.5 MB 28
    - CEMHD_press conference, 2009 November 24; 62.2 MB 123
    - Chancellors Awardees 20009, 2009 December 8; 12.6 MB 21
    - Santa Visit, 2009 December 9; 28.6 MB 54
    - Enrollment Management Awards, 2009 December 16; 18.7 MB 29
    - Haitian Memorial Ceremony, 2010 January 26; 185.7 MB 220
    - Tartarstan Delegation, 2010 January 27; 38.5 MB 95
    - S0B_GE, 2010 February 2; 55.9 MB 119
    - Haitian Discussion_Father Joseph Phillipe, 2010 February 3; 19.1 MB 25
    - Ferocious Feast_Big Purple Growl, 2010 February 6; 66.8 MB 121
    - Ferocious Feast_Big Purple Growl, 2010 February 6; 586.1 MB 486
    - Advocacy Day 2010, 2010 February 8; 174.0 MB 202
    - Advocacy Day 2010, 2010 February 8; 139.3 MB 284
    - MLK_2010_Susan Taylor, 2010 February 10; 87.8 MB 117
    - Marvin Press Event_SOB_business climate, 2010 February 23; 58.1 MB 77
    - Policy Conversation with SUNY Chancellor, 2010 March 2; 41.3 MB 101
    - Chartwells Food Show_10, 2010 March 10; 63.4 MB 121
    - Friends Exhibit, 2010 March 10; 43.2 MB 61
    - Friends Exhibit, 2010 March 10; 43.2 MB 61
    - Michael Brennan Lecture, 2010 March 11; 41.7 MB 62
    - Refuge Conversation Progam, 2010 March 12; 54.6 MB 70
    - Middle States Evaluation Team, 2010 March 17; 57.6 MB 74
    - Theresa Pardo_CTG_Brown Bag Lunch, 2010 March 18; 40.6 MB 85
    - ASP, 2010 March 18; 58.0 MB 79
    - Census_hand print event, 2010 March 23; 74.2 MB 170
    - Howard Dean_Karl Rove_Debate, 2010 April 7; 316.7 MB 599
    - Howard Dean_Karl Rove_Debate, 2010 April 8; 316.7 MB 599
    - Howard Dean_Karl Rove, 2010 April 8; 101.4 MB 186
    - Burton Lecture, 2010 April 20; 28.9 MB 35
    - Earth Day Events, 2010 April 22; 72.0 MB 82
    - President's Breakfast with Business Leaders, 2010 April 23; 45.8 MB 102
    - Awards of Excellence, 2010 April 23; 31.1 MB 50
    - Fountain Day 2010, 2010 April 26; 80.2 MB 90
    - Fountain Day 2010, 2010 April 26; 80.2 MB 90
    - Fountain Day 2010, 2010 April 26; 80.2 MB 90
    - Connecting the Dots Planning for Education, 2010 April 27; 8.8 MB 16
    - Vital Volunteer Luncheon, 2010 May 1; 66.5 MB 147
    - Great Dane Awards, 2010 May 3; 80.6 MB 171
    - Bread and Roses, 2010 May 6; 35.7 MB 87
    - Hindelang Lecture, 2010 May 12; 17.6 MB 42
    - Torch_Photo Service, 2010 May 13; 40.9 MB 79
    - Time-Dollar Program, 2010 June 7; 31.6 MB 81
    - United Way_Arbor Hill, 2010 June 10; 18.1 MB 45
    - Sexual Assault Conference, 2010 June 22; 61.4 MB 163
    - Small Business Forum with Rep. Paul Tonko, 2010 July 8; 65.4 MB 85
    - IFW_2010, 2010 July 15; 23.5 MB 26
    - Cancer Center Summer Students, 2010 July 23; 105.2 MB 273
    - Fullbright Gateway_2010, 2010 August 9; 11.0 MB 8
    - Giants Scholarship recipient, 2010 August 17; 29.0 MB 46
    - Explore UAlbany Program, 2010 August 27; 19.0 MB 38
    - Explore UAlbany_Pres. Philip and Mayor Jennings, 2010 August 27; 132.2 MB 117
    - MPA Welcome event_panel discussion, 2010 August 27; 163.6 MB 85
    - Virtual Media Guide, 2010 August 30; 113.0 MB 187
    - Welcome Back Pizza Party, 2010 August 30; 59.3 MB 53
    - Hannah's Hope_Sames Family, 2010 September 2; 72.3 MB 138
    - SEFCUmoneymachine_Explore UAlbany, 2010 September 3; 12.4 MB 18
    - Karen Hitchcock Portrait Unveiling, 2010 September 17; 175.9 MB 323
    - SPH_25th Anniversary Open House, 2010 September 24; 93.4 MB 183
    - reception for visiting researchers, 2010 October 6; 15.3 MB 35
    - Alumni Awareness Luncheon_10, 2010 October 8; 6.9 MB 24
    - Scholarship recipients and donors, 2010 October 8; 90.6 MB 226
    - freelance, 2010 October 9; 1.2 GB 1053
    - SA_Barbara Walters, 2010 October 9; 222.4 MB 281
    - Legacy Reception, 2010 October 9; 1.2 GB 1053
    - Business Leaders Breakfast, 2010 October 26; 99.8 MB 172
  - 2015 Welcome Week Events, 2015 August 21-2015 September 26; 6.2; 844
  - Commencement, 2009 May 16-2016 June 16; 6.3; 3036
    - Commencement, 2002 December 8; 223.6 MB 40
    - Alumni Affairs: 5/15/04 @ 5:30 - 6:30 PM location TBA Precommencement Dinner / Legacy, 2004 May 18; 48.0 MB 31
    - Alumni Affairs: 5/15/04 @ 5:30 - 6:30 PM location TBA Precommencement Dinner / Legacy, 2004 May 18; 48.0 MB 31
    - Commencement: 12/11/05 @ 2 PM RACC December Commencement, 2005 December 27; 436.1 MB 122
    - Commencement: 3/23/06 @ 9:30 AM studio Grads in Gown_ Christy Smith and Brian Goodale, 2006 April 6; 97.0 MB 88
    - Media and Marketing: 5/8/06 @ 4:45 PM studio three students in commencement robes for web feature, 2006 May 23; 50.8 MB 48
    - Commencement: 11/6/06 @ 10 AM to retake photos of Brian Goodale and Christy Smith of the Graduate Studies Office with UAlbany's Official regalia with new robes with a slight color change in the University seal., 2006 November 6; 123.3 MB 53
    - Commencement: 12/10/06 @ 1 PM RACC for Winter Commencement ceremony, 2006 December 10; 78.7 MB 215
    - Rockefeller College: 5/20/07 @ 12:30-2 p.m. Milne Hall, Downtown Campus for Commencement Ceremony, 2007 May 21; 81.3 MB 166
    - Commencement: 5/19/07 @ 9 AM SEFCU Area for Graduate Commencement Ceremony 5/20/07 @ 10 AM Lawn of the Science Library for Undergrad Commencement Ceremony, 2007 May 21; 67.7 MB 114
    - Commencement: 5/19/07 @ 9 AM SEFCU Area for Graduate Commencement Ceremony 5/20/07 @ 10 AM Lawn of the Science Library for Undergrad Commencement Ceremony, 2007 May 21; 67.7 MB 114
    - University Events: 12/9/07 from noon till 3:30 p.m. to take photos of December commencement., 2007 October 25; 122.8 MB 286
    - President's Office: 10/11/07 at 2:30 to take shots of Fall Faculty meeting in the Campus Center., 2007 October 25; 25.8 MB 43
    - University Events: 12/9/07 from noon till 3:30 p.m. to take photos of December commencement., 2007 October 25; 122.8 MB 286
    - University Development: Photo session: 5/17/08 at 9:00 AM in the SEFCU Arena for Graduate Commencement Photo session: 5/18/08 at 10:00 AM at the Science Library lawn for Undergraduate Ceremony, 2008 May 17; 2.4 GB 478
    - Rockefeller College: Photo session: 5/18/08, 12:30-1:30 PM for Undergraduate Commencement at Rockefeller College, Page Hall., 2008 May 18; 736.3 MB 130
    - Commencement Reception_School of Ed, 2008 December 8; 24.6 MB 33
    - Commencement Brunch, 2008 December 8; 17.4 MB 34
    - Winter Commencement 2008, 2008 December 8; 18.4 MB 27
    - Winter Commencement 2008, 2008 December 8; 18.4 MB 27
    - Lavender Graduation, 2009 May 15; 93.0 MB 38
    - Graduate2009, 2009 May 16; 131.6 MB 223
    - Undergrad_2009, 2009 May 17; 308.7 MB 180
    - Undergrad_2009, 2009 May 17; 231.6 MB 336
    - saved, 2009 December 7; 540.9 MB 339
    - Winter Commencement 09, 2009 December 7; 540.9 MB 339
    - Graduate Commencement2010, 2010 May 15; 273.6 MB 310
    - undergraduate commencement2010, 2010 May 16; 312.7 MB 436
  - Homecomings, 2013 October 19-2015 November 17; 6.4; 966
    - Homecomings, 2013 October 19-2015 November 17; 6.4.1; 966
      - Homecoming_08, 2000 February 3; 2.2 GB 655
      - Alumni Affairs: 6/20/02 @ noon Milne 2nd Floor Alumni Anniversary Luncheon digital, 2002 July 4; 71.6 MB 57
      - Alumni Affairs: 6/4/2004 and 6/5/2004 various locations and times Alumni Weekend 2004 digital, 2004 June 21; 1.9 MB 2
      - Alumni Affairs: 10/9/04 @ 12 Noon - 2 PM RACC Homecoming Tailgate Party and Game start digital, 2004 September 2; 178.9 MB 127
      - Alumni Affairs: 10/9/04 @ 12 Noon - 2 PM RACC Homecoming Tailgate Party and Game start digital, 2004 September 2; 178.9 MB 127
      - Alumni Affairs: 10/9/04 @ 4:15 - 5:15 PM Standish Room / Science Library Legacy Reception digital, 2004 September 14; 66.0 MB 47
      - Alumni Affairs: 2/16/05 @ 7:30 AM Life Sciences Bldg. 2nd fl lobby breakfast and tour / alumns digital, 2005 January 25; 87.7 MB 57
      - Media and Marketing: 3/30/05 @ Noon CC Patroon Room Pres Hall with Student Athletes digital, 2005 April 13; 20.6 MB 11
      - President: 3/31/05 @ 10 AM Wadsworth Lab / Corning Tower Albany, NY President tours Wadsworth Lab digital, 2005 April 14; 107.2 MB 68
      - Media and Marketing: 3/31/05 @ 2 PM Pres Office Channel 6 video taping; Business Forward digital, 2005 April 14; 29.6 MB 20
      - Alumni Affairs: 4/9/05 @ 5:30 PM Desmond Hotel Latham, NY Milne / Alumni Event digital, 2005 April 20; 158.6 MB 109
      - Media and Marketing: 4/14/05 @ 12:30 Hall of Fame RACC Westchester area high school counselors w/ Pres Hall digital, 2005 April 20; 26.5 MB 18
      - Media and Marketing: 4/14/05 @ 12:30 Hall of Fame RACC Westchester area high school counselors w/ Pres Hall digital, 2005 April 20; 26.5 MB 18
      - Alumni Affairs: 6/3/05 - 6/4/05 various times and locations Alumni Weekend 2005 digital, 2005 June 16; 924.8 MB 505
      - Alumni Affairs: 10/8/05 @ various times and locations Homecoming_05 digital, 2005 October 17; 261.0 MB 104
      - Advancement Events: 10/8/05 @ 9:30 AM Standish Room President's Champagne Brunch digital, 2005 October 18; 279.4 MB 108
      - University Development: 12/20/05 @ 11AM Alumni House Potter Club Alumns, 2006 January 3; 106.4 MB 18
      - Alumni Affairs: 10/20/06 - 10/21/06 various locations Homecoming 2006, 2006 October 10; 709.7 MB 387
      - Alumni House: Homecoming 2007: Tailgate, Football game crowd shots and various Alumni class events / Sat. Oct. 13, 2007 from 3 - 9 p.m., 2007 October 14; 298.1 MB 276
      - Alumni House: Homecoming 2007: Tailgate, Football game crowd shots and various Alumni class events / Sat. Oct. 13, 2007 from 3 - 9 p.m., 2007 October 14; 298.1 MB 276
      - Homecoming_08, 2008 October 25; 2.2 GB 655
      - Alumni Awards Gala, 2009 May 2; 75.0 MB 181
      - Alumni Association, 2009 May 3; 121.7 MB 167
      - Alumni Awareness Luncheon_09, 2009 October 10; 474.2 MB 257
      - Alumni Awareness Luncheon_09, 2009 October 10; 474.2 MB 257
      - Alumni Excellence Awards Gala, 2010 May 1; 129.8 MB 285
      - Homecoming_Fall Festival, 2010 October 9; 1.2 GB 1053
    - 2015 Homecoming, 2015 October 9-2015 November 17; 6.4.2; 710
- Portraits, 2006 June 1-2016 July 15; 7; 1296
  - Portraits, 2006 June 1-2016 July 15; 7.1; 1296
    - Media and Marketing: 3/28/03 @ 11:30 AM studio re-creation shot for case statement publication digital, 2003 April 11; 4.9 MB 16
    - Ctr for Women in Government: 6/30/03 studio portraits of Directors digital, 2003 July 10; 5.4 MB 8
    - Ctr for Women in Government: 6/30/03 studio portraits of Directors digital, 2003 July 10; 5.4 MB 8
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; 22.8 MB 32
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; 58.6 MB 86
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; 26.3 MB 42
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; 22.8 MB 32
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; 9.5 MB 17
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; 9.5 MB 17
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; 58.6 MB 86
    - Portraits, 2003 August 7; 26.3 MB 42
    - Business: 8/6/03 @ 1:30 PM Studio cover photo for viewbook transparency and digital, 2003 August 21; 83.9 MB 127
    - Portraits, 2003 September 6; 249.2 MB 84
    - Portraits, 2003 September 13; 285.2 MB 113
    - Portraits, 2003 September 19; 104.8 MB 89
    - Portraits, 2003 September 19; 12.5 MB 10
    - Portraits, 2003 September 19; 12.5 MB 10
    - Portraits, 2003 September 19; 104.8 MB 89
    - Portraits, 2003 October 3; 41.0 MB 36
    - Portraits, 2003 October 3; 41.0 MB 36
    - Portraits, 2003 October 30; 584.9 MB 112
    - Media and Marketing: 10/28/03 @ 3 PM CC Ballroom President's Address to Faculty digital, 2003 October 30; 374.0 MB 61
    - Portraits, 2003 October 30; 584.9 MB 112
    - Advancement: 1/7/04 @ 2:30 PM 25 East Bayberry Rd. Glenmont, NY portrait: Joy and Kenneth Ford digital, 2004 January 19; 41.0 MB 36
    - Advancement: 1/7/04 @ 2:30 PM 25 East Bayberry Rd. Glenmont, NY portrait: Joy and Kenneth Ford digital, 2004 January 19; 41.0 MB 36
    - Media and Marketing: 6/16/04 @ 2 PM Clock Tower James Czebiniak and car digital, 2004 June 30; 46.8 MB 25
    - Media and Marketing: 6/16/04 @ 2 PM Clock Tower James Czebiniak and car digital, 2004 June 30; 46.8 MB 25
    - Media and Marketing: 6/16/04 @ 2 PM Clock Tower James Czebiniak and car digital, 2004 June 30; 46.8 MB 25
    - Outreach: 7/12/04 @ 9;15 am 12 Sheridan Ave Albany Sharon Dawes w/ Tom Griffen digital, 2004 July 14; 90.6 MB 69
    - Business: 8/26/04 @ 12:30 BA-220 MBA head shots digital, 2004 August 11; 58.9 MB 192
    - Media and Marketing: 8/3/04 @ 12:30 PM Schenectady, NY portrait: Carmella Batista digital, 2004 August 17; 55.9 MB 36
    - Center for Legislative Development: 10/28/04 @ 10 AM 423 State Street portrait: Bob Nakamura digital, 2004 November 9; 82.9 MB 71
    - Media and Marketing: 11/1/04 @ 1:00 pm Cobb Room / Main Library portrait: Mr. And Mrs. Sheppard digital, 2004 November 15; 39.4 MB 21
    - Media and Marketing: 12/1/04 @ 1 PM Alumni House students with gonfalons and flags digital, 2004 December 13; 103.7 MB 66
    - Media & Marketing: 1/11/05 @ 2 PM CC 137 portrait: Nancy Bellowitch-Negron digital, 2005 January 25; 44.1 MB 25
    - Media and Marketing: 1/24/05 @ 1:30 PM Lecture Center Delores Cimini with students digital, 2005 February 7; 59.6 MB 58
    - Media and Marketing: 1/31/05 @ 3 PM 332 Loudonville Rd. Loudonville, NY portrait: Terri Boor and Ed Mayer digital, 2005 February 8; 60.5 MB 41
    - Media and Marketing: 5/19/05 @ 2 PM Parent's Fountain Mr. and Mrs. Shepherd / Mr. and Mrs. Ostoyich digital, 2005 June 2; 98.5 MB 51
    - Media and Marketing: 5/19/05 @ 2 PM Parent's Fountain Mr. and Mrs. Shepherd / Mr. and Mrs. Ostoyich digital, 2005 June 2; 98.5 MB 51
    - Media and Marketing: 5/19/05 @ 2 PM Parent's Fountain Mr. and Mrs. Shepherd / Mr. and Mrs. Ostoyich digital, 2005 June 2; 98.5 MB 51
    - Media and Marketing: 5/31/05 @ 11 AM Selkirk, NY portrait of Marie Wideman digital, 2005 June 14; 114.6 MB 77
    - Research: 6/1/05 @ 10 AM studio photo for Research Report digital Kerry Gavin/Mary Fiess, 2005 June 15; 42.8 MB 40
    - Media and Marketing: 6/1/05 @ 11:30 studio Bonnie Steinbock digital, 2005 June 15; 39.9 MB 85
    - Media and Marketing: 7/14/05 @ 2:30 PM Freedom Quad Vince Porforio Digital, 2005 July 29; 120.2 MB 79
    - President: 8/16/05 @ 1:15 PM Facilities Management Bldg. Service Bldg. B Chiller Photo Op digital, 2005 August 29; 59.0 MB 37
    - President: 8/18/05 @ 11:30 AM Media and Marketing Office Suite Pres Hall presents Val DiRocco with winnings from horserace winnings digital, 2005 September 1; 17.0 MB 11
    - Provost: 9/8/05 @ 9:00 AM - 10:30 AM Location TBA Compact Planning Workshop digital, 2005 September 1; 58.0 MB 41
    - University Development: 8/23/05 @ 11:50 Giant's Practice Field portrait: Al Baker digital, 2005 September 6; 29.8 MB 18
    - Business: photo sessen: 8/25/05 @ 12 Noon BA 220 MBA head shots digital, 2005 September 8; 439.1 MB 177
    - Media and Marketing: 9/7/05 @ 2:30 PM Collins Circle Tom Birkland attaching UAlbany decal digital, 2005 September 21; 54.0 MB 36
    - ZAKHAR~1, 2005 December 8; 25.5 MB 36